A Guide to the Director's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1926-1933
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Oversize Materials (Box 35-36)
  - Statement of Salaries, 1932 September 13 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Status of Waterfowl Season, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Summary of Results Financially, 1926 July 1 - 1932 June 30, 1932 December 21 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Untitled Ledger, 1931-1932 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Warden Reports of Convictions, Fines, and Costs, Fiscal Year Ending 1928 June 30 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Annotated Map of Virginia, undated [1] (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Annotated Map of Virginia, undated [2] (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Announcement: Sale of Valuable Real Estate, 1930 April 4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Attachments: Letter from J.J. Dizulaitis to W.E. Carson, 1932 March 25 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Comparative Statement of Activity, 1931 April 30 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Drawing: Water Lines for State Fish Hatchery Leffler Springs Craig County, 1929 June 17 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Ledger Pages by District, 1927 June (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Ledger Pages by District, 1927 July (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Map: Natural Bridge National Forest (U.S. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service), 1924 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Map: Natural Bridge National Forest - attachment to letter dated 1931 July 7 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Map: Streams and Watershed Areas, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Shipping Lists by District, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Summary by Division of Reports of Convictions, Fines, and Costs of Game Wardens Fiscal Year ending 1927 June 30 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - "Tear Sheets" - letters to A. Willis Robertson, 1929 and undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Topographic May: Passage Creek Drainage Area - Attachment to letter from J.T. Dirzulaitis to W.E. Carson, 1932 May 24 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Untitled Record of Hunting Seaons with Species, Dates, and Limits, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)